

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced Business Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in Health Information System (HIS). Skilled in Customer Service, Software System Analysis, Databases, System Architecture and Training. Strong research professional with a Master of Science ( ) focused in Computer and I ation Systems from Assumption University.

#### CONTACT

PHONE:

#### **SKILLS**

System Analysis and Design.

Operation systems: Windows, Mac, Linux.

Virtualization: VMware, Citrix Xen

Database: MS SQL, MySQL, Mongo DB.

Core Network.

Communication and Negotiation Skills.

Teamwork.

Deadline Control.

# NGUYEN NGOC HOA

### IT Manager

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Assumption University of Thailand (ABAC)

Master of Science Computer Information Systems (2007).

## Ho Chi Minh University of Foreign Language and Information Technology (HUFLIT)

Bachelor of Science Computer Information Systems (2005).

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### [Bernard Healthcare] [IT Manager] November 2021 to present

- Responsible to ensure the operational level of ALL IT and communication equipment and systems in Clinic, implementing and maintaining clinic policies regarding IT Security (ISO 27001), Backup (Veeam) and infrastructure Purchasing, support the company to keep usability capabilities.
- System architecture for 2 clinics (HIS, RIS, PACS, LIS, CRM, Patient portal, Disaster Recovery Site ...)
- Manage product backlog.
- Consulting ROI, costs and risk.
- Contact point with the vendor.

#### [Gugotech Corp] [Business Analyst] July 2021 to November 2021

• System analysis and design for Clinic Information System and Booking online.

#### [Lac Viet Computing Corp] [Senior Business Analyst] October 2018 to May 2021

- System analysis and design for Health Information System (HIS), Laboratory Information System (LIS), Radiology Information System (RIS), Personal Health Record (PHR) & Healthcare Big Data.
- Collected information form stakeholder and translated to technical team.
- Created UX and prototype for web and mobile.
- Technical research and protocol (HL7 FHIR, ASTM, DICOM, LOINC, SOP...).
- UAT support, training and dealing change requests.
- IT Infrastructure Consulting.
- Digital Transformation Consulting
- Pre Sales

#### [Family Medical Practice] [Clinic IT Manager] November 2011 to August 2018

• Responsible to ensure the operational level of ALL IT and communication

equipment and systems in Clinic (hardware, software, domains, VOIP, PBX and Video conference), implementing and maintaining clinic policies regarding IT Security, License, Backup and infrastructure Purchasing, support the company to keep 24/7 usability capabilities.

- Contact point with the vendor.
- Computer's network and intranet- Designing and developing. Developing a maintenance plan (via internal resources and external contractors).
- Security solutions and Backup solutions for an EMR and financial software-Designing, developing a maintenance plan (via internal resources and external contractors) and developing from local to corporate level.
- Hardware and infrastructure for local and corporate network- tendering and managing maintenance efforts (via internal resources and external contractors).
- Software for the Medical information flow- Managing purchasing, licensing and developing efforts to ensure the concept of apaperless hospital (among them PACS, DR/CR, EMR, patients flow, financial etc.
- Telecommunication, VOIP and Video systems- Designing and developing, tendering and purchasing efforts. Developing a maintenance plan (via internal resources and external contractors).
- Integration of Low voltage and Medical communication systems (labels printers, barcode printers and readers, nurse call system, electronic directions boards, queue managing displays, employees position control etc.).

#### [Lam Quoc Ltd] [IT Manager] January 2009 to November 2011

- Manage the company systems and handheld device.
- Analysis, design and implement the building core network and CCTV.
- Customer services.

#### [Military Information Technology Institute] [Assistant Research] November 2007 to July 2008

- Applied research into information technology for military, air traffic manages, alert systems, queue management systems, high buildings control.
- Training and coaching military officers.